a midlife crisis might scare some but
not me
Jason - the only plus side to my mom's
terrible news is the new cause it gave
me in life here's the thing I told Jason
that I found a lump on my back and it
turned out it was actually this big knot
and my masseuse got it out like in two
minutes
I didn't tell him the second part that
kid needs to get his together so I
put everything I regret not doing into
an urn bow to empty it before I fill it
back up it's now my goal to not only be
the well-respected youtuber you know but
to become the middle-aged inspiration
you deserve because even a guy like me
Jason Nash could use a second chance
my pickup mom mom you know what I'm
gonna finally confront a bully
that's like I thought of them leaving
nasty comments on my YouTube videos you
know what good for you
cuz I can't begin to count the number of
times that you came home from school
crying to me I never cried okay whatever
you say listen I gotta go I got a thing
I never cried so that's it's probably
some sort of dementia or I don't know
why she said that that was weird
he cried he was a weirdo honestly I
don't blame those boys at all Jason
sorry mr. Nash you asked me to find some
more mild You Tube commoners for you to
confront okay I I never said mild pretty
clear that you didn't want anybody to
mean oh I am excited to prove myself to
mr. Nash and just really be a sponge
during this production I know I only get
three college credits but the
satisfaction of doing a good job that's
priceless
this first one is you look like Ellen
DeGeneres with a meth addiction problem
okay
that one's a little mean yeah also
weirdly worded 46 more like 406 okay old
died okay die that's
actually the thing I shall find it
myself honestly I didn't realize there
was a lot of mentions of skulking him
which I'm even know was a thing and then
I looked it up and do not Image Search
that unless you're into that I don't a
king shame oh my god okay this is it
poon blaster
421 six hours ago you think there's like
400 Tony other ones who taught them how
to use the internet at the old folks
home Oh piece of dirt okay here's what
we do get this guy out here into this
house and have a confrontation
okay come on in so it's great that
you've set a day for your confrontation
but there's no shame in getting some
confrontation of competence counseling
first okay well full disclosure I'm
already a very confident guy so I'll be
treating this is more of a refresher
course sure um did you bring in the
rough draft of the computational
monologue I asked you to write I don't
need the monologue C confidence I've
helped a lot of people with my monologue
methods so if he feels like he doesn't
need one
then it's my job to show him that he
does let's do some role-playing
I'll pretend to be your bully and then
you confront me without a monologue okay
listen I don't appreciate the comments
that you left on my people look like you
have a plastic bag under your skin like
somebody put a plastic bag on your face
and then wrapped your skin around it hey
if you could role play someone who
doesn't make fun of my looks
right off the bat no no I'm not gonna do
that cuz that's what they would usually
go for first especially with a person
that looks like you my methods are a
little unconventional
sometimes I when I'm a little boots up I
can get carried away yeah take a seat
let's dive in
[Music]
you have no power you are not funny
stupid oh okay
bummer that's our hour oh are you sure
yep that's how that's how timers work
all right best of luck with that bully
Jason okay yeah thanks hey um how long
should that monologue be do I think he's
gonna do well with his bully no no no no
no that bully's gonna tear him apart
okay shut up
sorry it's my dog he's a Maltipoo and he
has just been all over the
floor all day I'm not using the
monologue it's only there for a last
resort yeah
boom blaster 421 we finally meet
it's really you hi I'm Marcus hi
what's with the tuxedo for the award
show oh yeah yeah come on in Clutton
okay come in for a second I shall check
this out I invited boom blaster four to
one to Los Angeles under the false
pretense that he won a contest to be my
plus-one and a fake award show no I
can't let him pretending to be nice to
me with me so I'm gonna confront the
out of that kid hey I don't mean to
be sappy but you having me out here
means the world to me I don't have a ton
of friends and dad walked out ten years
ago to buy a pack of cigarettes and
eventually died of lung cancer and you
know I do watch your videos all the time
and sometimes it feels like you're the
closest thing I have to like a real
friend Oh
sorry sorry about your dad that's okay
smoking so much she's a real piece of
mine too yeah yeah a liar he was a
liar yeah well we'll get to all that
yeah I gotta go drop a deuce real quick
so I'm saying buddy hi you almost out of
there um Marcus has got a little
surprise for you so okay bye he's
definitely with me do you like
it I thought I'd just seen up a little
okay I think you're cute huh you can
suck my ass have a seat here does this
look familiar you are a bully and today
I am here to confront you did you read
all of it yeah I read all of it of
course it all in read more what's what's
read more to read more it's more of a
comment just kidding big Finn
love your videos it's a joke Josh okay
the reason that it's about goop
okay well here's the deal um there is no
award show I I made it up
so I could go confront you on my
internet show so you're free to go if
you want to can stay and all my savings
on this tuxedo and a plane ticket and
you just want me to go we got it I just
got here and cleaned your house and I
and you want me to go perfect listen
here bully I am here today to confront
you I'm a bully
you brought a 16 year old fan here
so you could disappoint them
as a pulley you really hurt my feelings
and I won't stand for it stay off my
comments page can old oh how dare you
hey Bob we did it did you see me
confront him yeah bro we did it I
thought he was a bully when you arrived
and he was definitely a bully when he
left and that's what counts
bully confronted look to clean in here
though yeah you know I definitely do
have the same vibe at all
you